[Music]
thank you
welcome everyone
this is the active inference Institute
quarterly Round Table number three in
2022 it is September 28 2022.
welcome to the active inference
Institute
the active inference Institute is
dedicated to learning researching and
applying active inference you can find
us at some of the links here on this
slide
this is recorded in an archived live
stream so please provide us with
feedback so we can be improving our work
all backgrounds and perspectives are
welcome and we'll be following video
etiquette for live streams
today in the quarterly live stream
number three we are going to have a
three broad sections they won't be too
long there will be a lot of time if you
want to add any other notes in the live
chat or maybe even if anybody wants to
um
say hi in live chat and join the uh live
stream itself we're going to first have
Institute scale updates we'll talk about
some changes in development at The
Institute level we'll then talk about
projects and the Education and Research
Endeavors that we've been involved in
and that have been developing over this
quarter and then we'll close with some
next steps and affordances for getting
involved
let's go first to the active inference
Institute aii updates at The Institute
scale
all right I'll just give a some overview
and then Alex or Yvonne feel free to add
more
we're continuing to work with fried
Frank in a pro bono capacity
to help with the legal side of
formalizing our incorporation as a
non-profit
we are formalized in terms of what
members we have our five founding
members and some of our governance
structures
currently we are on the stage of
selecting and electing the board of
directors so at this point at the end of
September 2022 we are extremely actively
seeking self-nominations as well as
suggestions for people who might like to
serve in the board of directors
especially with expertise or experience
serving on board of directors for
non-profits and any other relevant
experience related to governance
Financial non-profit Education and
Research
following the selection of the board of
directors the board will then select
officers who are in uh more of a direct
operations role at The Institute
and we've also joined the Delaware
Alliance for non-profit advancement Dana
to provide us with access to non-profit
resources and support
Alex or Yvonne want to give any comments
if you're talking Alex you're muted but
I see yellow
okay
okay carrying forward
We are continuing to develop our
Institute branding
first we are working with some external
expertise
on some logo and brand redesigns for The
Institute
this is really exciting and more will be
announced when the work here is ready to
be shown
so enjoy the black white and red and the
current fonts and layouts that we have
while you can
they'll still be there they'll still be
around
and we've also updated our website with
a restructured short description of the
Institute which I'll just read now and
then Alex rivon please make any extra
comment or provide any context
the active inference Institute is
dedicated to learning researching and
applying active inference we provide
avenues for connection and integration
with broad audiences and disciplines
the active inference Institute provides
a setting for people to Aid each other
in pursuit of a better understanding of
active inference
The Institute organizes education
research and communication
to advance the progress and public
awareness of Frontier knowledge in
active inference and closely related
topics
we structure our strategy with the
building blocks of participatory open
science
accessibility and service to our
epistemic community
wanna yes
yeah sure
uh as a as a institution we are educated
to
um having understanding or in a broad
audience about active inference what is
it why how
we can use it and
as we know that active inference is
applicable for a lot of fields and
domains
we are open to the community from ho ho
all of those fields and their names
thanks yeah
agreed that one of the best ways for a
connection to be made between active
inference and some other field is
kind of the micro engagement when people
from that field get involved and get
involved in learning and then they'll
see all these affordances for connecting
active inference theoretically and in
practice to their area it's not like
there's just a tree and the connections
are ready to be pulled at First Sight
it's takes a little integration and
including different communities in the
conversation so that's what we're happy
to be building and working on and also
in a participatory way
where people's feedback is really
welcome and people's engagement is
essential so we'll continue with a few
more notes on the Institute scale and
then we'll talk more about projects that
are happening at the Institute all of
which people can get involved in if they
would like
so just a structural note
uh as a summary
the focus and functions of our Institute
are research education Outreach and
engagement and methods
and these Foci are playing out across
multiple scales
there's the participant scale which is
the human and their engagement with the
Institute
there's the Institute scale which is the
system of interest that we're able to
enact policy in at The Institute level
and there's our broader epistemic
Community which includes the really
exciting and growing active inference
community and all the amazing
developments happening in that area as
well as more broadly and
um more distally many adjacencies that
have been identified or have not been
identified ranging from neuroscience and
medicine to machine learning computer
science ecology robotics all these
amazing areas we have discussions around
and we have two organizational units
that are kind of like departments they
are organizational constructions that
help us
coordinate projects and efforts and
allocate attention around our two
primary missions in Foci which are
research and education so Azure active
is the organizational unit that hosts
education projects whereas the Research
Unit hosts research projects and we uh
we joked about having a a kind of
competition or an opening of window for
renamings but as anyone who has watched
these roundtables know we show up on the
day of with what we know that day
so your engagement or suggestions and
ideas are always welcome and that's how
we update that's how we learn
but that's just reflecting some of our
structural learning and updating
that's the Institute level anything else
to add here Alex driven or we'll
continue on to the project scale
all right let's talk first about
education
this is going to be education at the
Active inference Institute and project
updates over Q3 2022.
first
the active inference textbook group
so we've been having two concurrent
cohorts of the active inference textbook
group the first cohort of the textbook
group began in May 2022 and over the
following three months they completed
the first five chapters of the textbook
and now that first cohort the Intrepid
adventurers the early foragers are
continuing on in chapters six through
ten which is where the textbook turns
towards model building and recipes for
model construction which has been really
exciting
and we also in September of 2022 began
the second cohort of the active
inference textbook group so this is some
people who are rejoining from the first
cohort as well as many many new people
joining in
and it's another concurrent cohort
that's starting from the beginning of
the book so this is the kind of minimal
templating of a continuous delivery
textbook group format where as more and
more people are interested and curious
to learn about active inference and
increase their familiarity and
competency in engaging and positive
social environments we will be able to
have the familiarity
of people who have taken the cohort
experience of the textbook group before
to then return for example as
facilitators or in other roles and
therefore scale The Continuous delivery
of textbook group experiences around the
par pazulo and friston 2022 textbook but
also around other texts that may be
arising
where as we work as a group
we're in a shared epistemic Niche and we
provide a whole host of value-added
services that deeply enrich your
learning so if you're currently spending
one or more hours per week or month
curious about active inference
especially curious about this textbook
your learning and your contributions
will be leveraged if you join a textbook
group cohort
we curate and we compile and address
questions that we're having relating to
different parts of the textbook
and we've created just an amazing
repository of questions that grows every
day
and they contain questions that are
confirmatory and basic what does this
word mean here or what do you think this
means all the way on up to speculative
and research oriented or application
oriented questions so questions are
really important part of learning and
they're a really important part of the
textbook group
and also through being in the textbook
group one becomes more familiar with a
variety of ontology scaffolded learning
approaches that we use in the active
inference Institute related to our work
from the very beginning with the active
inference ontology so for example here's
equation 2.5
with a variational free energy
and here we have just a screenshot of
what The annotation looks like
in the shared knowledge resource in the
coda for those who are learning and
discussing equation 2.5 and there's a
whole host of other information
questions that people are having and
what does this mean and what are the
relations to other areas but this kind
of a learning environment allows people
who have different backgrounds in math
or the formalisms or in some of these
other theoretical domains that come into
play in relationship with active
inference to have a really exciting
space where we're all learning a ton so
it's been awesome to have two
concurrents cohorts going in the
textbook group and we're looking forward
to in the close of 2022 to have the
first cohort complete the book
and then have a second cohort get up to
the midpoint and then in the beginning
of 2023 we will likely continue with the
second cohort chapter 6 through 10 and
begin a third cohort and see where
things are at in the active inference
world then
any comments or thoughts on the textbook
group
yeah sure
uh textbook group is very valuable
tradition for education and when you
learn something and you get feedback
from your peers you have more
understanding and in our groups we are
providing a lot of useful instruments
that help to understand not so clear
Theory as active inference
awesome and one kind of note or seed for
the future is the textbook is open
source which is awesome it increases the
accessibility and downloadability
but it also offers some incredible
future opportunities in terms of
remixing the book transposing the
content into GitHub
re-rendering translating doing some
amazing secondary work with a textbook
and again seeing that as templating for
future versions or other textbooks so
that's the textbook group
onwards we go
on once once again the main goal of this
activity is to help understand our main
idea and we plan to do this activity on
a regular basis and you can join us
wherever you want and wherever you are
ready
thank you Yvonne very true
all right in July 31st 2022 we had our
second applied active inference
Symposium on robotics
there were two live streams of about
four hours each
and there were a handful of
co-organizers from within the Institute
and from outside the Institute
we had a whole range of formats
presentations roundtables and
discussions
the two sessions are shown here
and I'll uh when somebody else is
talking make sure to post the links in
the YouTube live chat so people can go
check them out or they're available just
on our live stream Coda page
um
there were about nine
presentations of around 20 to 30 minutes
each people talking about specific
applications of active inference so if
you're wondering where is active
inference being applied or how can
active inference be applied this
Symposium gives nine case studies and
settings from the robotics domain
where active inference is being applied
today and tomorrow
and at the end of each session we also
had a round table discussion that was
really interactive and connected the
dots and provided some context beyond
the more research-oriented presentations
that were happening for the bulk of the
presentations so for those who are
interested in applications of active
inference or in robotics this was a
really exciting event and this is also
we hope a tradition to continue applied
active inference symposia
where people who want to co-organize or
present on their applications in
Knowledge Management or in
medicine or in ecology we can convene
and coordinate around the symposia and
have different formats
so we're currently working to transcribe
the products of this Symposium and make
them citable proceedings
any thoughts you have on this you
fellows
I think that
robotics in terms of Applied field is
one of the most straightforward
application of active inference
and possibly
and future providing
real
breakthroughs in results of robots that
will be used
active influences from work for where
Robotics cognitions and so on and as we
said from web communication there are
different groups of researchers all over
the world
we are interested in communication they
are interested in in presence in results
and hopefully more people next years
will join in with robotics active
influence robotics movement
and some dates in some days some close
future
we'll see
really great application and
like autonomous robots based on active
inference
awesome thank you
all right speaking of the active
inference Journal so the goal of the
active inference Journal is to increase
the accessibility and the indexability
citability and utility of live streams
and various audio visual material
produced in and around the active
inference Institute
So currently we've been working on
around four specific streams and events
to improve and template our process that
we're hoping to build and scale on
further
what we do in the journal is we take the
outcomes of the live stream the audio
visuals of the live stream
and we get a primary artificial
intelligence AI generated transcript and
then engage in a sequence of enrichments
editing and curations so we edit the
transcripts by listening carefully to
the audio and making sure that the
speaker's sense is to the extent
possible captured
and then we also develop for example
appendices and other scholarship around
the document so when somebody mentions a
paper or when somebody mentions a person
those kinds of information can be
included and the discourse can be
connected to the active inference
ontology in cases where the terms are
being used
and
again that will enable more accessible
searching in the language of the live
stream for example people have asked
questions that somebody might want to
query again or might want to hear
someone's response at a given time too
and cite that or just learn from it and
then also it's really important to have
such standardized pipelines for
transcription in order to enable
translation into different languages
ways that you can get involved in the
journal if you're interested or curious
in this area whether you have editing or
proofreading experience or not
there are many affordances to edit
transcripts so listening carefully to
the audio and providing suggested edits
on texts
and also we're especially interested to
research and develop methodologies for
the journal process
so anyone familiar or curious about AI
assisted transcription and translation
modular Publications decentralized
science and DSi the usage of git as a
versioning system any of these areas we
would welcome your engagement in the
journal project because that's the
direction that we want to head and that
is what is going to unlock some of the
potential of the 200 plus live streams
that we've already carried out and the
many hundreds that we'll carry out in
the future
it will enable these past and future
live streams
to be able to be searched cited
translated and used more broadly
so if you want to join the meetings for
the journal project they're on Mondays
at 13 UTC in our Discord
so a few next steps I mentioned before
but I'll just give a quick shout out to
um at carpathy who recently for the Lex
Friedman podcast
spun up a site using the open AI whisper
platform
and made transcripts for all Lex
Friedman episodes
and so we imagine something similar
because in our
Coda for the live streams we have 200
plus
Journal discussions research
presentations we are ready to be open AI
whispered or other Pipelines
so if that is something you're curious
about or carpathy or others if you want
to come get involved you're absolutely
welcome there's a lot of learning and
accessibility and rigor that can be
improved with these kinds of rapidly
emerging text engineering developments
any other comments you want to make on
active Journal
yes and this 200 plus
videos there are a lot of
a lot of useful information that's very
valuable and if it will be extracted it
will move forward while we
or how we understand it both episodes
totally agreed there's ways of saying
and conversing in the live streams
that certainly are clearer
restatements of and developments beyond
what is in the written literature so
especially as we move towards a
multimedia future
and a more participatory and inclusive
science sector it's important that we
have the systems in place
with low human bandwidth to be able to
improve and distribute scholarship on
these topics
All Right Moving On to the live streams
themselves so we had uh one month off in
July from live streams
where we just chilled read other papers
not these papers
um and then we've had a bunch of great
live streams so far in Q3
we had guest streams with Brett Anderson
with Ronan tamari at all and with John
verveiki
and we discussed papers in the live
stream series on an active cognition
abductive logic and active inference and
active inference as ecological
communication
we also have a wide range of really
interesting live streams coming up
including on Bayesian mechanics on
neural networks on all kinds of areas of
active inference application and a lot
of really exciting theoretical
developments also so if you want to be
involved in live streams
in the YouTube live chat you'll find the
past and upcoming streams so one way to
get involved is to watch listen share
comment and be involved that way if you
want to play a role for example speaking
on a live stream or helping contribute
to the preparation around the live
stream that can also be incredibly
important as well as making connections
and recommendations for whom we should
invite so that we can have a really
powerful and diverse range of guest
streams and papers selected for the live
streams so live streams have continued
in their educational function
and just wanted to highlight
um each one of these projects there have
been many people to mention and I hope
that we can
um
by next quarterly lab meeting have some
clearer Pathways for making those clear
but just wanted to it in bulk
acknowledge everybody who contributes to
the weekly meetings for live stream
preparation and organizing and those who
join the stream as well as those who
help prepare content
and coordinate questions for the live
stream in the background and may not be
on the video themselves so that's the
live streams we continue on there any
other comments
just once again uh one obvious think the
more you the more you uh
involved in any any of any our activity
and live streams is uh
extremely extremely useful for
understanding and
to see the way of application affect
this inference the more you're engaged
the more you understand this topic
great point
and sometimes just scanning the titles
of the papers that we discussed in the
50 papers that we have discussed almost
50 by the end of the year
um
these are curated selections usually
with the authors joining and almost
always with a DOT zero video where
people who cared made background in
context to make it as accessible as
possible so this is a unique Learning
Resource if you have a regime of
attention and availability or capacity
for these topics or you're curious and
think you might it's going to be a
really unique Learning Resource for you
to check out our past videos and then if
you're curious about media production
communication you want to explore short
formats you'd like to facilitate a
discussion in a non-english language
you want to make an animation video
there's so many affordances that we can
support So if you're curious about those
areas just get in touch
okay continuing on
education internal systems thinking
ongoing activity uh Yvonne let's I'll
let you describe it
thanks
yes so we also have not actually related
the active inference
our activity and this August we launched
uh four weeks session for assistant
thinking
course part of it that related to the
role Concepts
uh
we for four weeks we can't cover the
whole the course
foreign
just a second
uh
we can't cover the whole course but four
weeks for understanding the role concept
is uh fair enough time
possibly also also run this October next
cohort and for previous one we have
um good feedback for um from our
participants
could use uh could you show next slide
please thank you
and
next this October we start a new cohort
and here is a link for participation
will also it will also take four weeks
and during this week's we consider
uh concerts from system thinking
course yeah and
I will apply these Concepts to the ER
Pro to your projects or maybe
for even live projects
and next one we we have this
uh activity with our partner
Institute for augmented intelligence in
entrepreneurship engineering and
management
and this fall The eam Institute launched
for courses now these courses are
available for free and we also encourage
you to
um
discount discourses for sure you will
find a lot of
a lot of useful information also related
to the active inference as a
evolutionary theory
awesome yes so this system's
engineering and systems thinking
activity helps us learn about roles and
how to apply them in projects and we are
applying them in active inference
Institute projects so it also upskills
participants and gets them ready to take
on more involved and responsible roles
in our Institute and it's all a
co-evolutionary dance as The Institute
formalizes and gains resources and
establishes itself in the niche then
such roles will also be the ones that we
can support
all right any other comments
onto the research so the previous
updates were from education just to
Briefly summarize textbook group two
ongoing cohorts
active inference robotics Symposium with
eight hours of presentations and
discussions
active inference Journal working towards
accessibility and indexability of all of
our speech products
live streams continuing
and systems thinking education activity
ongoing open to all of these projects
your involvement
on to the research
so it's been a great quarter for
research
first we'd like to highlight our active
block prints development
active block prints is an open source
package that is implementing classic and
novel active inference models within the
system simulation framework of cadcat
so we have a few updates on active block
prints first Jakob smickle presented a
poster at the iy 2022 third
international workshop on octave
inference so congratulations Jacob for
this awesome poster presenting it in
person and to all others who have been
contributing to development on octoblock
prints it's um
really great to see the development of
this project and also a lot of other
work in the active inference community
so please check out iy if you're curious
to see what is Cutting Edge in active
inference research they really did a
great job in getting some of the best
projects in the space
um also
active blockference has received
um some funding through the git coin
gr15 round that just completed
so our git coin project
was
active block prints an open source
package for cognitive modeling in web 3.
and uh we specifically framed how we
could utilize cognitive modeling
approaches integrating active inference
and cadcad for cognitive modeling in
web3 ecosystems
so big appreciation to everyone who
provided even one
dollar to this funding opportunity and
in several weeks we'll know the final
amount that we've received after the
quadratic funding algorithms have all
been applied but suffice to say that we
have some money in our tank to develop
active block prints so there are many
ways and areas people can get applied in
there are weekly meetings there are
weekly meetings at 12 and 17 UTC on
Wednesday in the Discord and also we
discussed this
um with Jacob today Mondays at 18 UTC is
going to be a code development specific
session so if you want to get a little
bit more Technical and collaborate with
Jacob and others on the cad CAD active
inference modeling then Mondays 18 UTC
is a great synchronous time
at 12 and 17 UTC on Wednesdays those are
slightly more open sessions where we can
also split off and have a technical
development but we talk about a whole
range of areas so I'm going to mention
some areas and then tasks and how we're
going to use some of our funding to
accelerate development
these are just showing a few of the
areas where we believe cognitive
modeling could be used or might be
important or relevant to consider
ranging from a range of social settings
education governance legal online work
stigmergy so on
to a host of web 3 cases so Dows
decentralized Finance d-school DSi
ethereum a lot of other areas in web 3
and then also
uh on the ground
with the ants
in terms of developing the active infra
ant model for ant colony foraging and
ultimately larger task allocation
questions
these are all areas where we see the
active block runs package
as being able to address them eventually
and what it takes to address an active
lock for its model in one of these cases
and settings is for someone with domain
expertise or knowledge to provide the
Bridge Building from one side and then
the package to develop the generalized
capacities from the other side so we're
working from both ends to enable really
powerful domain-specific applications of
active inference while building modular
structure of the active block fronts
package so that those functionalities
can be used in other settings for
example a navigation setting that might
arise from our work on Ant foraging
might be used in a different context in
another non-ant setting so that's a
little bit about how we approach the
development of the package we think
about the functionalities of the package
modulars as modules that can be invoked
and functions that can be called
and then we develop different settings
for cognitive modeling
there are a range of tasks that people
can get involved in
ranging from cadcat and active inference
technical tasks to a whole host of
package level and documentation and
Community engagement tasks so if this
sounds like a cool direction or you
would just like to learn more then
please join a synchronous meeting or get
in touch another way because this is a
super exciting area of development we
hope that active block prints can be a
really important package in this area
and so
come be involved
with the funding what we're going to be
experimenting with in the coming weeks
and months is a task based payment
scheme
so individuals or small teams will prom
will propose
how much funding they would like to
receive for what specific tasks and
there's a form that will be filled out
and so we can show you that if you join
synchronously completing that form will
raise your task requests to
consideration
and then if the task is approved and you
complete it as laid out you will be paid
the amount that you requested so if
funding ever felt like it was a rate
limiting step for your involvement in
learning or applying active inference
and contributing to open source public
goods then
consider it differently now because we
can support this type of work
and we also see some really exciting
opportunities for people for example to
propose tasks around applying to other
grants or to including more developers
or more documentors or people who want
to make active block runs live streams
there's a million areas where people can
develop here so join the weekly meetings
is the best way to get involved there
any other comments on blockfronts
foreign
last research update
this is not presenting all the research
happening in The Institute this is just
to kind of raise a few projects up
we have had a project on cognitive
modeling Frameworks and their
comparisons
the goal of this project is to
understand similarities and differences
with active inference and other
cognitive modeling Frameworks
so the approach that we're taking here
is to review and assess different
cognitive modeling Frameworks
in terms of their features their
functions
their elements their areas of
application and so on
and that will help us understand
similarities and differences amongst
Frameworks as well as more formally
and historically integrate active
inference with other models
so this is one of a research task that
could open up quite broad Vistas for
application
anyone who's curious or engaged in
cognitive modeling would be welcome to
get involved with this project
and one can even see the pathway here
kind of like the epistemic chaining
example in pi mdp
if someone identifies that there's a
common cognitive modeling framework
that has features ABC
and is used in domain f
then
domain F becomes an area of application
for active inference if functions ABC
can be implemented better in active
inference than the initial framework
so that kind of work on the landscape of
cognitive modeling is a really important
precursor to understanding where and how
and with an emphasis on which
functionalities
it even makes sense to talk about
applying active inference
and we hope and expect and prefer that
there will be active inference
applications that haven't been within
the range of traditionally considered
cognitive settings for example I'm not
sure how often in multi-scale ecology
cognitive modeling Frameworks are used
as a simulation tool
now we know that active inference is
being applied in those areas
but there are also areas where cognitive
modeling is already happening
and it may or may not be using active
inference so those represent adjacencies
whereby developing the connection
between how they're doing it today and
how it could be done
people will be opening up really large
areas for active inference application
and also massive areas of attention and
support
so this is kind of a cool Direction
any notes on this or anything else on
Research
all right let's just go to some last
steps and close
if anyone in the live chat has any
questions they're welcome to add them
so next steps for The Institute well
on the engagement and Outreach Frontier
we continue to grow and develop
we host most of our Communications at
our Discord
which has over 450 members now
uh our Twitter as well as our podcast
and video channels are all growing in
terms of their niche
so if you
support us on any of these platforms and
can share or just even tell one person
that can be quite helpful and always
provide us with feedback on how we can
improve our environmenting our
engagements with external interfaces
and then just to provide a summary of
some steps and directions for how we go
from Q3 on Beyond to Q4
any of these areas if you are interested
or curious please be involved the
earlier and the more involved simply the
better and the higher leverage point
that is for the future
We are continuing education and research
it's the main focus of the active
inference Institute and we will always
continue education and research
we're also during these months
undergoing a really creative
and unique organizational development
opportunity for example around
assembling the board of directors and
some of the early decisions around
governance and organizational structure
so if you have input or want to be more
involved here as well otherwise just to
know that it's happening
we are looking towards several
directions
in the end of 2022 and to really come
into in a new way in 2023
we're looking towards increased
participation in projects and learning
groups as well as the development of an
internship program that will help
structure your engagements with a mentor
and in a Project Specific way so that
you can stay engaged and also have
something clearer to point to about your
engagement with the Institute
We are continuing to as we finish the
first cohort of the textbook group think
more and more about active inference
course development so we'd encourage
anyone who wants to partner or be
involved in that area to get in touch in
the journal project and in a slightly
different way in the textbook group
we're working towards the captioning the
subtitles and language translations
where possible
and especially with our new
organizational structure we're looking
towards funding opportunities and
Partnerships so if you have any thoughts
or capacities
or feedback in these areas they're all
super important areas for The Institute
going forward and it would be really
appreciated as we are a participatory
open Science Institute and only recently
received our first small amount of
funding through the get coin grant for
Block prints to explore new avenues of
partnership funding service and beyond
that we have not done so what hasn't
happened yet
is not too strong of a prior on what we
may do in the future
if that makes sense we'll be doing
different things and I hope that you can
be a part of it because it grows and
changes in co-engagement when and only
when people get engaged that's
interactionism this is not
instructionism
so if you have any
excitement around these topics or any
others that you would want to have on
here then getting in contact with us
will be a great first step join our
Discord join any of the synchronous
meetings
email us and we can start a conversation
that way
well that is all
for this round table it was a short
quarter
it was only like
few months
from our previous live stream
time went by quite fast
and a lot did happen so
once again next next for the promises to
the uh more active and
as you understood they are very open to
participation
so see you in the class see you on our
our synchronous meetings in Discord
subscribers and share
yes Alex any last comments
um I can only repeat that
the participation of people who will
join us in future is the main focus for
us and everything we what we are doing
is related to help others to
learn about active influence to learn
active inference and find ways to apply
it and we are on open and endedness path
and actually we
we don't know what will be in in three
months from here but we will adopt and
provide the
possible affordances for hours
to join and learn
so welcome
indeed welcome to those who are and
haven't joined yet
and a big appreciation again for
everyone who's contributed through the
Institute to make things how they are
today
so thanks Yvonne and Alex
see y'all later
thank you thank you